<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>devops.com.co</title><link>http://devops.com.co/</link><description>Recent content on devops.com.co</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 14:15:36 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://devops.com.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sync Vscode Extensions</title><link>http://devops.com.co/posts/sync-vscode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 14:15:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/posts/sync-vscode/</guid><description>It’s been a long time since my personal computer was reinstalled I just remember that it was 3 years ago when I was having problems with my LUKS configuration, sadly I was unable to solved it so I just reinstall all my operative system entirely. Now recently I just finish a clean Debian install, I was refreshing my Gnu/Linux Laptop and all the tools. the thing here is that I was looking to have the same visual studio code settings in my new install.</description></item><item><title>Install a Package Manager on Windows Dev Enviroment</title><link>http://devops.com.co/posts/install-pkg-manager/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:15:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/posts/install-pkg-manager/</guid><description>During a long time it’s been really dificult for me to work on Windows development enviroments, it was not a good sensation, but after giving a try during two months I’ve been able to work with, for my tremendous surprise there is a package manager out there, they’ve integrated a linux subsystem in the operative system and so many things more.
If you don’t know what key advantages you get when you use a package manager I will simple describe it as control, with a package manager you will have to install software and it will automatically download the appropriate package from its configured main software repository, install it, and set it up, all without you having to click through wizards or hunt down .</description></item><item><title>Welcome to my website</title><link>http://devops.com.co/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:15:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>This site is going to help me document things that I could forget and it will be my personal reference, The site is dedicated to sysadmin and devops first and foremost. You will also find a great deal of automation, CI/CD, containerization, coding, and etc. My post are going to be written in english and spanish languages.
Hope you enjoy this blog post.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>http://devops.com.co/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/about/</guid><description>Hello Everybody 😎, My name is Hector Fabio Jimenez Saldarriaga, but you can call me H or Hector. I’m from the beautiful🌠country of Colombia 🌎. I’m Currently working as an Infra/SysOps Engineer at a local company, with some awesome technologies like AWS, and a few regional Datacenters. I hold a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science and Systems Engineering, and also an Electrical Technology degree from Universidad Tecnológica de Pereira. I do really enjoy Computer Systems and everything related with electronics.</description></item><item><title>Contact me</title><link>http://devops.com.co/contact-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/contact-me/</guid><description>Follow me, @c1b3rh4ck twitter.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://devops.com.co/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://devops.com.co/projects/</guid><description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description></item></channel></rss>